<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on DominoPivot&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on DominoPivot&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020 DominoPivot. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.dominopivot.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifice (English version)</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/artifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/artifice/</guid>
      <description>Artifice (English version) All that defiles on your TV is just a scene You fantasize on CGI and on greenscreen Your concubines have a whole life behind their cups Bet you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recognize them without makeup
No hair around the cunt just shave your whole body Not fat, not flat, no muscles, none of that&amp;rsquo;s girly Or don&amp;rsquo;t you dare complain if you look plain ugly Couldn&amp;rsquo;t a lady have moment of mercy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop struggling with Microsoft Word</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/word/</guid>
      <description>Stop struggling with Microsoft Word I recently had to collaborate on a project which involved writing a boring report with Microsoft Word. The experience made me realize&amp;mdash;or rather reminded me how little most people know how to use it. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with you a few tips to make you much more efficient with Microsoft Word.
This article was written using Microsoft Word for Office 365 MSO (16.0.11629.20192) 32-bit. UI changes in further updates may not be accurately reflected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broken Chains</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/broken-chains/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/broken-chains/</guid>
      <description>Broken Chains This is a complaint for all things long gone And things that prevailed but have since gone all wrong This is a complaint for memories replaced With a fresh coat of paint that looks out of place
This is a prayer for good things to last And for a future as good as the past This is a prayer for getting better May this pile of mistakes help us climb much higher</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lies</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/lies/</guid>
      <description>Lies While a lie might grow awhile until it fools a whole people Chasing the truth like fools can be the root of great evil
How many wrongs are done in the name of good and god? Even the fruits of sin can fund a worthy cause And a tissue of lies cause one to fall in love
Love is an addiction that&amp;rsquo;s hard to get rid of
To fend off of an oppressor you fight fire with fire While fire can consume so can it warm the bed you lie in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bittersweet</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/sugar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/sugar/</guid>
      <description>Bittersweet When I&amp;rsquo;m bored as can be I buy sugar Low on energy I grab sugar When I get moody I eat sugar When I am lonely Spin spin sugar
When I feel salty I groan sugar When I&amp;rsquo;m unhappy I spout sugar When I am angry I spill sugar When life gets to me I cry sugar
When I can&amp;rsquo;t take it I hang on to what I know Sweet escapism</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beast in a Domino</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/the-beast-in-a-domino/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/the-beast-in-a-domino/</guid>
      <description>The Beast in a Domino Her school uniform A fake cover on a book A book she can&amp;rsquo;t show
The edge of her skirt Ultimate territory A convenient breeze
Her guilt-ridden smile A hint of her desires Her frilly panties
I can see under the disguise Masquerading your true essence I read between the lines of lies Your white white lies of innocence
When you&amp;rsquo;re alone the domino falls When no one else is watching you When you lay bare and topple the walls And no one is there to see you go bestial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pride</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/pride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/pride/</guid>
      <description>What is Pride Pride doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean considering yourself superior to others. It means not looking down, not feeling ashamed for who you are. It means keeping our head up in the face of adversity.
Pride is an event meant to honor those who fought for our rights and those who still do, those who suffer or even die because of discrimination. It&amp;rsquo;s an event meant to remind the world that discrimination still exists and that we need to fight against it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/stackoverflow-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/stackoverflow-guide/</guid>
      <description>A Guide to Stack Overflow Stack Overflow is a lot more complex, rich and interesting than you might expect from just browsing it. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had a problem with your code and looked online for help, chances are you landed on Stack Overflow. This Q&amp;amp;A-style website has answers for all the entry-level problems you will face when learning programming, so it&amp;rsquo;s possible you will never need to create an account and ask your own questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-dimensional Auditive Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/concepts/one-dimensional-auditive-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/concepts/one-dimensional-auditive-adventure/</guid>
      <description>One-dimensional Auditive Adventure One reason why I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to make a blog was to follow in the steps of Three Hundred and post video game concepts and ideas I never had the time to implement. This article is the first of hopefully many on the topic, and describes an idea which came to me while learning the basics of programming in college.
With my limited abilities at the time, I did some brainstorming about the kind of games I could render in a terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different games</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/different-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/different-games/</guid>
      <description>Different games A common question I get when I say I love video games is what kind of games do you play? and I never know what to answer. I am an experimentalist, my pleasure comes from discovering new things. I love playing games that surprise me. So for a first article on this blog I thought I would share with you some games that are quite unique and different. Games of all genres and on various platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colateral</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/cola/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/cola/</guid>
      <description>Colateral Quench my thirst, soothe this curse with just a slurp or two Let us venture together, surrender all virtue My savior is your flavor and we&amp;rsquo;re long overdue I wanna drown myself deep down a sea of you
Sweeter than any liquor our love is a perfect brew Popping bubbles in the skull on every rendez-vous Passion is just an addiction that we follow through I lust for tasting your perfection and blending with you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate and Vanilla</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/chocolate-and-vanilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/poems/chocolate-and-vanilla/</guid>
      <description>Chocolate and Vanilla Some time ago when you were young, an ice cream shop opened up. Even if you weren’t hungry, you followed your friends to the shop. But when the man at the counter asked you to pick a flavor, you said no thanks, I’ve just had dinner.
Some time ago when you were young, this ice cream shop opened up. Some of your friends were crazy for chocolate, so you hanged around there a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/credits/</guid>
      <description>Credits Material Design icons Icons from the Material Design icon set by Google used under Apache License 2.0
Copyright 2020 Google Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &#34;License&#34;); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>