<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on DominoPivot&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on DominoPivot&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020 DominoPivot. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop struggling with Microsoft Word</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/word/</guid>
      <description>Stop struggling with Microsoft Word I recently had to collaborate on a project which involved writing a boring report with Microsoft Word. The experience made me realize&amp;mdash;or rather reminded me how little most people know how to use it. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with you a few tips to make you much more efficient with Microsoft Word.
This article was written using Microsoft Word for Office 365 MSO (16.0.11629.20192) 32-bit. UI changes in further updates may not be accurately reflected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pride</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/pride/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/pride/</guid>
      <description>What is Pride Pride doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean considering yourself superior to others. It means not looking down, not feeling ashamed for who you are. It means keeping our head up in the face of adversity.
Pride is an event meant to honor those who fought for our rights and those who still do, those who suffer or even die because of discrimination. It&amp;rsquo;s an event meant to remind the world that discrimination still exists and that we need to fight against it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/stackoverflow-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/stackoverflow-guide/</guid>
      <description>A Guide to Stack Overflow Stack Overflow is a lot more complex, rich and interesting than you might expect from just browsing it. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had a problem with your code and looked online for help, chances are you landed on Stack Overflow. This Q&amp;amp;A-style website has answers for all the entry-level problems you will face when learning programming, so it&amp;rsquo;s possible you will never need to create an account and ask your own questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different games</title>
      <link>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/different-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dominopivot.com/blog/different-games/</guid>
      <description>Different games A common question I get when I say I love video games is what kind of games do you play? and I never know what to answer. I am an experimentalist, my pleasure comes from discovering new things. I love playing games that surprise me. So for a first article on this blog I thought I would share with you some games that are quite unique and different. Games of all genres and on various platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>